Chelsea, can I get some feedback?
For sure.
Lose weight but don't have time to cook?
Let me show you the lunch I have literally
every single day that-
Feel like we missed the opportunity to
show me this lunch because right now
you're
kind of pulling veg out the fridge. Cool.
And there is a bit of, ooh, what
are you going to make?
Let's try this again
Lose weight but don't have time to cook?
If you want to lose weight
but don't have time to cook
Let me show you the lunch I have
I have every single day.
Let me show you the lunch
that you could have every single
day. Let me show you the routine
that you could do every day,
rather than me
saying,
"This is the routine I do every day."
Literally every single day that takes-
The rustling,
if it's going to rustle coming out the
fridge, we could have said it
as an atrack. So this
is what you could've done.
You could've said it to the camera,
then you could've gone in,
taken the bag out,
then with that footage,
you've got the footage here of you taking
the bag out.
You've got you saying it.
You could overlay it like a J cut, and
that means that we wouldn't get this
rustle.
Five minutes to make,
has 50 grams of protein
And when we're saying 50 grams of protein
and 500 calories, we could showcase that
food.
I think it would just make it look so much
better.
People go, "Wow,
that right there?" Because this
is a form of hook, a visual hook.
You know like when you're watching a
YouTube video, it'll show you things
that are
coming up 20 minutes into the video to get
you to stay.
Weight is the fact that their time
is very much limited.
Okay, golden rule.
If we can cut any part of the video
and it still makes sense, we
should cut it.
And I feel like maybe we could have cut
that first bit.
Of Greek yogurt. To make your life easier,
why not get pre-cooked
chicken. This flavor's tikka,
and you're going to put in half a packet,
which turns
out to-
I'm sat here thinking,
"What am I waiting for?
What am I waiting for?" If you'd shown me
earlier in the video what's to come,
I can make a decision whether or not it's
going to be worth it.
It's going to make it nice and creamy,
and it's going to act as your sauce.
The second I see a wrap,
I'm thinking wrap foods are unreal.
You're telling me you're going to wrap
that up, maybe toast it, cut it in half,
show me the layers, and
that wasn't used in the hook.
You cannot have a wrap without cheese,
in my personal opinion.
So-
Melted cheese is to come.
How has this not been shown earlier on?
Shaun Casey, an absolute master at this.
He takes a bite out of it
and shows you it as the hook.
On there. Bob's your uncle.
You've literally made a high protein-
When wrapping a wrap,
fill the middle of the wrap.
The sides come in from both sides,
then you fold over and wrap.
Everything, in my eyes,
should be wrapped like a burrito.
It should be closed on both ends,
and I'll fight to the death over this.
And who doesn't toast a wrap with cheese
in it?
I'll tell you what,
let's have a look at old Shaun Casey. Oh,
frir.
Today I made and prepped a week's worth of
our fried lunches.
Preview.
This one is absolutely slap at a base.
He literally eats it and bites it
and showcases the whole experience of
it before even explaining it. This
is his hook.
Avocado.
Gentle.
And gives some to his dog. Bloody
flipping genius. Missed opportunity,
I believe, Chelsea.